intopicmedia.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy | InTopic Media

**INTOPIC MEDIA PRODUCT PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT:**

InTopic Media is a in-text logo and publisher-side technology company.

Publisher-side means that all of our solutions reside on the individual server of the websites we partner with.

InTopic Media technologies are not downloaded to a user’s desktop.

InTopic Media technologies do not upload personally identifiable information from a user’s desktop.

InTopic Media technologies do not collect or store any personally identifiable user information.

Corporate Website Privacy Statement (www.intopicmedia.com):

InTopic Media (“InTopic”) respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Website, www.intopicmedia.com (the “Website”). InTopic Media thus provides this privacy statement to explain what information is gathered during a visit to the Website and how such information may be used.

Use of Information: As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to the Website. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of InTopic Media’s Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience.

The Website may request that you give us contact information such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address; demographic information such as your age and gender; and personal preference information. Information submitted at the time of submission will be used by InTopic Media only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, including without limitation the improvement of our products, services and the contents of the Website. InTopic Media may also share such information with our business and promotional partners to further those interests. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties.

Access to Personally Identifiable Information: If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by emailing our Customer Support at info@intopicmedia.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

Specific uses of information on the Website may include:

**InTopic Media’s Inquiry Form**

InTopic Media Website contains an “inquiry form” for web publishers to request additional information about InTopic Media’s products/services. The inquiry form requires web publishers to give contact information (such as name and email address.) InTopic Media uses this information to contact Web Publishers about the services on the Website in which they have expressed interest.

Web Publishers have the option to provide demographic information (such as website address and vertical sector) to InTopic Media. InTopic Media encourages them to submit this information so it can provide them a more customized reply to their inquiry.

**Insertion Orders**

If an advertiser purchases a service from InTopic Media, InTopic Media requests certain personal and company identity information from the advertiser on the insertion form. Advertisers must provide contact information (such as name, company name, street address, email and telephone number) and financial information. InTopic Media uses this information to provide services and for billing purposes. If InTopic Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the advertiser.

**Web Publisher Service Agreement**

If a Web Publisher signs a service agreement, InTopic Media requires the Web Publisher to provide certain identifiable information including: name, company name, street address, email and telephone number. This information is necessary to process the Web Publisher’s agreement.

**Web Publisher Sign-up form**

When a Web Publisher signs a service agreement with InTopic Media, the Web Publisher is also required to provide company and personal identity information, commercial information, technical contact information and customization information to start their contextual advertising services. InTopic Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If InTopic Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Web Publisher.

**Advertising Network Service Agreement**

When a Advertising Network signs a service agreement with InTopic Media, the Advertising Network is also required to provide company, personal identity information and commercial information. InTopic Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If InTopic Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Advertising Network.  
**  
Service-Related Announcements**

InTopic Media will send Web Publishers service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. The only other e-mails we send out are in response to feedback, contact and sign-up form submissions.

Generally, a Web Publisher may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If a Web Publisher does not wish to receive these communications, they have the option to deactivate their account according to the terms of their Web Services Agreement.

**Customer Service**

Based upon the provided personally identifiable information, InTopic Media will send Web Publishers a welcoming email to verify their username and password and to set up their account. InTopic Media will also communicate with them in response to their inquiries, to provide the services they request, and to manage their account. InTopic Media will communicate with Web Publishers by email or telephone, in accordance with their wishes.  
**  
Testimonials**

If your name appears in a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information displayed there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these testimonials.

**Legal Disclaimer** : InTopic Media may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with InTopic Media’s rights or property, other users of the Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. InTopic Media may also disclose user information when necessary to comply with a court order, legal process or other legal proceeding.

**Children Age 12 and Under** : InTopic Media recognizes the special obligation to protect personally identifiable information obtained from children age 12 and under. AS SUCH, IF YOU ARE 12 YEARS OLD OR YOUNGER, InTopic Media REQUESTS THAT YOU NOT SUBMIT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE OR TO INTOPIC MEDIA. If InTopic Media discovers that a child age 12 or younger has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete that child’s personally identifiable information from our records.

**Use of Cookies** : Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Website easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Website, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please consult the technical information relevant to your browser for instructions. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Website may not function properly or may be considerably slower.

**Links to External Websites** : InTopic Media is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites not owned or controlled by InTopic Media. InTopic Media is also not responsible for any information that you might share with such linked websites. You should refer to each such website’s respective privacy policy and practices prior to disclosing any such information.

**Choice/Opt-Out** : The Website may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list in order to discontinue any such future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, please follow the specific instructions set forth within the communications you receive from InTopic Media which you no longer wish to receive. If you are unsuccessful in completing the instructions specified in any such communication, please e-mail us at info@intopicmedia.com, including a copy of the undesired email attached to the request, and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list.

Contact Information for Questions, Comments and Complaints: If you have any questions, comments or complaints about www.intopicmedia.com or about this privacy statement, please contact:

Tradewind Media, LLC dba InTopic Media, 1170 Howell Mill Rd., Suite 210, Atlanta, GA 30318, U.S.A. and email: info@intopicmedia.com.

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to InTopic Media such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

**Security** : Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, InTopic Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit via the Internet. By transmitting any such information to InTopic Media, you accept that you do so at your own risk.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact info@intopicmedia.com.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms** : By using the Website, you accept the policies and restrictions set forth in this Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Website. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

_Last updated December 22th, 2009_
